{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy M21', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 5 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '20 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 + One UI 2'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Black Shark 3 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 13 MP (ultrawide) + 5 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '20 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei P40', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) omnidirectional + 8 MP (telephoto) 3x optical zoom + 16 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide) + IR TOF 3D, (biometrics sensor only)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 (AOSP + HMS) + EMUI 10.1'}
{'device_name': 'Realme X3 5G', 'manufacturer': 'realme', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 + Realme UI'}
{'device_name': 'LG K51S', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide) + 5 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0'}
{'device_name': 'LG K41S', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, (wide) + 5 MP, (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo iQOO Neo 3 5G', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 + iQOO UI 1.0'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei P40 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) Periscope (telephoto) 5x optical zoom + 40 MP (ultrawide) + TOF 3D, (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide) + IR TOF 3D, (depth/biometrics sensor)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 (AOSP + HMS) + EMUI 10.1'}
{'device_name': 'Honor 9X Lite', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 + Magic UI 3'}
{'device_name': 'Lenovo Legion', 'manufacturer': 'Lenovo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 16 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'Motorized pop-up 20 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10 + Legion OS'}
{'device_name': 'Poco F2 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Poco', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP depth sensor'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '20 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 + MIUI 11'}
{'device_name': 'Motorola Moto G8 Power Lite', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie)'}
{'device_name': 'TCL 10 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'TCL', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 16 MP (ultrawide) + 5 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '24 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 + TCL UI'}
{'device_name': 'Infinix S5 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Infinix', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP + 2 MP + QVGA low light camera sensor'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'Motorized pop-up 16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Black Shark 3', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 13 MP (ultrawide) + 5 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '20 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0'}
{'device_name': 'Honor 8S 2020', 'manufacturer': 'Honor', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie) + EMUI 9, Google Play Services'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo S6 5G', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 + Funtouch 10.0'}
{'device_name': 'OPPO Find X2 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 13 MP (telephoto) + 8 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 + ColorOS 7'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy S20 Ultra', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '108 MP (wide) + Periscope 48 MP (telephoto), 1/2.0, 0.8Âµm, PDAF, OIS, 10x hybrid optical zoom + 12 MP (ultrawide) AF, Super Steady video + 0.3 MP, TOF 3D (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '40 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 + One UI 2'}
{'device_name': 'TCL 10 5G', 'manufacturer': 'TCL', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 5 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 + TCL UI'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy M01', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10 + One UI 2'}
{'device_name': 'HTC Wildfire R70', 'manufacturer': 'HTC', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP, (wide) + 2 MP, (macro) + 2 MP, depth sensor'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9 (Pie)'}
{'device_name': 'Realme 6i', 'manufacturer': 'realme', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 8 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 + Realme UI'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo A52', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro ) + 2 MP depth sensor'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 + ColorOS 7.0'}
{'device_name': 'Realme C3', 'manufacturer': 'realme', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP + 2 MP depth sensor'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy A21', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide) + 5 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 + One UI 2.0'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Redmi K30 Pro Zoom', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 8 MP (telephoto) 3x optical zoom + 13 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'Motorized pop-up 20 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 + MIUI 11'}
{'device_name': 'Meizu 17', 'manufacturer': 'Meizu', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 12 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 5 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '20 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10 + Flyme 8.1'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo A12e', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP + 2 MP depth'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 (Oreo) + ColorOS 5.1'}
{'device_name': 'Honor 9S', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10 + Magic UI 3.1, no Google Play Services'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Redmi Note 9 Pro Max', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 5 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 + MIUI 11'}
{'device_name': 'Honor 9C', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10 + EMUI 10.1, no Google Play Services'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy Z Flip', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP + 12 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '10 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 + One UI 2'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo A12', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP + 2 MP depth'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie) + ColorOS 6.1'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy M11', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide) + 5 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 + One UI 2'}
{'device_name': 'Honor 9A', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide) 5 Mp (ultrawide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10; Magic UI 3.1, no Google Play Services'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo Reno3', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 13 MP (telephoto) 2x optical zoom + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP B/W'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '44 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 + ColorOS 7'}
{'device_name': 'LG Q51', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide) + 5 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Poco X2', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2MP (dedicated macro camera) + 2 MP (depth sensor)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '20 MP + 2 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 + MIUI 11'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE nubia Play', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 + nubia UI 8.0'}
{'device_name': 'Google Pixel 4a', 'manufacturer': 'Google', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.2 MP (wide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo Reno3 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 13 MP (telephoto) 2x optical zoom + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP B/W'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '44 MP (wide) + 2 MP depth'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 + ColorOS 7'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy A31', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 5 MP (macro) + 5 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '20 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 + One UI 2'}
{'device_name': 'Apple iPhone SE (2020)', 'manufacturer': 'Apple', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP (wide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'iOS 13'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Redmi Note 9', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 + MIUI 11'}
{'device_name': 'Motorola Moto G8 Power', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide) + 8 MP (telephoto) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0'}
{'device_name': 'Honor View30', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '40 MP (wide) + 8 MP (telephoto) 3x optical zoom + 8 MP (ultrawide) lenses'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) sensor'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 + Magic UI 3'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo A92', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro ) + 2 MP B/W'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 + ColorOS 7.1'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo A31', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie) + ColorOS 6.1'}
{'device_name': 'vivo NEX 3S 5G', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 13 MP (telephoto) 2x optical zoom + 13 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'Motorized pop-up 16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 + Funtouch 10.0'}
{'device_name': 'Honor 30', 'manufacturer': 'Honor', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '40 MP (wide) + Periscope 8 MP (telephoto) 5x optical zoom + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 (AOSP + HMS) + Magic UI 3.1'}
{'device_name': 'Honor Play 4T', 'manufacturer': 'Honor', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 (AOSP + HMS) + Magic UI 3.1'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy M51', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 12 MP (ultrawide) + 5 MP (macro) + 5 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10 + One UI 2.0'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo iQOO 3 5G', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 13 MP (telephoto) + 13 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 + iQOO UI 1.0'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Redmi Note 9 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 5 MP (macro) + 2 MP depth sensor'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 + MIUI 11'}
{'device_name': 'Honor Play 4T Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Honor', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 (AOSP + HMS) + Magic UI 2.1'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Mi 10 Lite Zoom', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (telephoto) + 8 MP (periscope telephoto) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 + MIUI 11'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo V19', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 + Funtouch 10.0'}
{'device_name': 'Honor View30 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '40 MP (wide) + 8 MP (telephoto) 3x optical zoom + 12 MP (ultrawide) lenses'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) sensor'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 + Magic UI 3'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy J2 Core (2020)', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo (Go edition)'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Redmi 8A Dual', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP + 2 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie) + MIUI 11'}
{'device_name': 'Honor 20e', 'manufacturer': 'Honor', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '24 MP + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie) + EMUI 9.1'}
{'device_name': 'TECNO Camon 15 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Tecno', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP + 3 other unspecified cameras'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 + HIOS 6.0'}
{'device_name': 'Motorola Moto G8', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP + 8 MP + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Redmi 8A Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP + 2 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie) + MIUI 11'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE Axon 11 5G', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '20 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 + MiFavor 10'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy M31', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 5 MP (macro) + 5 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 + One UI 2.0'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy A71 5G', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 12 MP (ultrawide) + 5 MP (macro) + 5 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 + One UI 2'}
{'device_name': 'Blackview BV9900 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Blackview', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48MP+5MP+16MP+2MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Infinix S5 lite', 'manufacturer': 'Infinix', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP + 2 MP + AI Lens (low light sensor)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie); XOS 5.5'}
{'device_name': 'LG Velvet', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 5 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (standard)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10 + LG UX 9'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy S20', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP, (wide), Dual Pixel PDAF, OIS + 64 MP, (telephoto), PDAF, OIS, 3x optical zoom + 12 MP, (ultrawide), AF, Super Steady video'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '10 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 + One UI 2'}
{'device_name': 'TECNO Camon 15', 'manufacturer': 'Tecno', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP + 3 other unspecified cameras'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 + HIOS 6.0'}
{'device_name': 'Motorola Edge Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '108 MP (wide) + 8 MP (telephoto), 3x optical zoom + 16 MP (ultrawide) + TOF 3D (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '25 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Redmi Note 9S', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 5 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 + MIUI 11'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo Ace 2', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP B/W (depth) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 + ColorOS 7.1'}
{'device_name': 'Ulefone Armor X6', 'manufacturer': 'Ulefone', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie)'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Mi 10 Youth 5G', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + Periscope 8 MP (telephoto) 5x optical zoom + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 + MIUI 12'}
{'device_name': 'TECNO Camon 15 Premier', 'manufacturer': 'Tecno', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 5 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (depth) + QVGA cameras'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'Motorized pop-up 32 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 + HIOS 6.0'}
{'device_name': 'Ulefone Armor 7E', 'manufacturer': 'Ulefone', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide)+ 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie)'}
{'device_name': 'OPPO Find X2', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 13 MP (telephoto) + 8 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 + ColorOS 7'}
{'device_name': 'Sony Xperia 1 II', 'manufacturer': 'Sony', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP (wide) + 12 MP (telephoto) 3x optical zoom, OIS + 12 MP (ultrawide) + 0.3 MP, TOF 3D, (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei P40 Pro Premium', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '52 MP (wide) Periscope (telephoto) 10x optical zoom + 8 MP (telephoto) 3x optical zoom + 40 MP (ultrawide) + TOF 3D, (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 (AOSP + HMS) + EMUI 10'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Mi 10 5G', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '108 MP (wide) + 13 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP depth sensor'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '20 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 + MIUI 11'}
{'device_name': 'Honor 8A Prime', 'manufacturer': 'Honor', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie) + EMUI 9'}
{'device_name': 'Lava Z71', 'manufacturer': 'Lava', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP + 2 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie)'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy S20 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP (wide) Dual Pixel PDAF, OIS + 64 MP (telephoto) PDAF, OIS, 3x hybrid optical zoom + 12 MP (ultrawide) Super Steady video + 0.3 MP, TOF 3D, (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '10 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 + One UI 2'}
{'device_name': 'OnePlus 8', 'manufacturer': 'Oneplus', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) (OIS+EIS) + 16MP Ultra Wide + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 + OxygenOS 10.0'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy S20 5G', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP, (wide), Dual Pixel PDAF, OIS + 64 MP, (telephoto), PDAF, OIS, 3x optical zoom + 12 MP, (ultrawide), AF, Super Steady video'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '10 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 + One UI 2'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo Reno3 Vitality', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP B/W + 2 MP depth sensor'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 + ColorOS 7'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Redmi 10X 4G', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP depth'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 + MIUI 11'}
{'device_name': 'Honor 30S', 'manufacturer': 'Honor', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 8 MP (telephoto) 3x optical zoom + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 (AOSP + HMS); Magic UI 3.1'}
{'device_name': 'Motorola Moto G Power', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0'}
{'device_name': 'alcatel 1B (2020)', 'manufacturer': 'Alcatel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 (Go edition)'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei nova 7 SE', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 + EMUI 10 with HMS (no Google Play Services)'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei P30 lite New Edition', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP depth sensor'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie) + EMUI 9.1'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo Reno3 A', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (depth) + 2 MP B/W'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 + ColorOS 7.1'}
{'device_name': 'Nokia 5310 (2020)', 'manufacturer': 'Nokia', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'VGA'}, 'front_camera': {}, 'operating_system': 'N/A'}
{'device_name': 'Nokia 5.3', 'manufacturer': 'Nokia', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide), 5 MP, (ultrawide) + 2 MP, (macro) 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei P40 Lite', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (wide) dedicated macro camera + 2 MP depth sensor'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 + EMUI 10'}
{'device_name': 'Sony Xperia 10 II', 'manufacturer': 'Sony', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP (wide) + 8 MP (telephoto) PDAF, 2x optical zoom + 8 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0'}
{'device_name': 'Honor 30 Pro Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Honor', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) omnidirectional + Periscope 8 MP (telephoto) 5x optical zoom + 16 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 (AOSP + HMS) + EMUI 10.1'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy A51 5G', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 12 MP (ultrawide) + 5 MP (macro) + 5 MP depth sensor'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 + One UI 2'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Y7p', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP depth sensor'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie) + EMUI 9.1'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Redmi K30i 5G', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '20 MP (wide) + 2 MP depth sensor'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 + MIUI 11'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Mate Xs', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '40 MP (wide) + 8 MP (telephoto) + 16 MP (ultrawide) + TOF 3D, (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'No - uses main camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 + EMUI 10.0'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy S20 Plus 5G', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP (wide) Dual Pixel PDAF, OIS + 64 MP (telephoto) PDAF, OIS, 3x hybrid optical zoom + 12 MP (ultrawide) AF Super Steady video + 0.3 MP, TOF 3D (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '10 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 + One UI 2'}
{'device_name': 'Red Magic 5G', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 + Redmagic 3.0'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei P40 Pro Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) omnidirectional + Periscope 8 MP (telephoto) 10x optical zoom + 8 MP (telephoto)3x optical zoom + 40 MP (ultrawide) + TOF 3D(depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide) + IR TOF 3D, (depth/biometrics sensor)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 (AOSP + HMS) + EMUI 10.1'}
{'device_name': 'OPPO Find X2 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) omnidirectional PDAF, Laser AF, OIS Periscope 13 MP (telephoto) 5x optical zoom, PDAF, Laser AF, OIS + 48 MP, f/2.2, 17mm (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 + ColorOS 7.1'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy S20 Ultra 5G', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '108 MP (wide) + Periscope 48 MP (telephoto), 1/2.0, 0.8Âµm, PDAF, OIS, 10x hybrid optical zoom + 12 MP (ultrawide) AF, Super Steady video + 0.3 MP, TOF 3D (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '40 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 + One UI 2'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Redmi K30 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 5 MP (telephoto) 2x optical zoom + 13 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'Motorized pop-up 20 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 + MIUI 11'}
{'device_name': 'Realme Narzo 10', 'manufacturer': 'realme', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP B/W'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 + Realme UI'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei nova 7i', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (wide) dedicated macro camera + 2 MP depth sensor'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10 + EMUI 10'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo A72', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 M (depth) sensor'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 + ColorOS 7.0'}
{'device_name': 'Lenovo K7', 'manufacturer': 'Lenovo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0'}
{'device_name': 'Realme X50 Pro 5G', 'manufacturer': 'realme', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 12 MP (ultrawide) + 8 MP (macro) + B&W'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP + 8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 + Realme UI'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Mi 10 Lite 5G', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 5 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 + MIUI 11'}
{'device_name': 'alcatel 1V (2020)', 'manufacturer': 'Alcatel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide) + 5 MP depth sensor'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0'}
{'device_name': 'alcatel 1S (2020)', 'manufacturer': 'Alcatel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide) + 5 MP (ultrawide/depth sensor) + 2 MP (dedicated macro camera)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo Find X2 Neo', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 13 MP (telephoto) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP B/W'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '44 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 + ColorOS 7'}
{'device_name': 'Nokia 8.3 5G', 'manufacturer': 'Nokia', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP, (wide) + 12 MP, (ultrawide) + 2 MP, (macro) + 2 MP, (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '24 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 + Android One'}
{'device_name': 'OPPO Find X2', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 13 MP (telephoto) + 12 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 + ColorOS 7.1'}
{'device_name': 'Infinix Hot 9', 'manufacturer': 'Infinix', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth) + QVGA (Low light sensor)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 + XOS 6.0'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Mi 10 Pro 5G', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '108 MP (wide) + 8 MP (telephoto)  PDAF, Laser AF, OIS, 10x hybrid optical zoom + 12 MP (portrait) 2x optical zoom + 20 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '20 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 + MIUI 11'}
{'device_name': 'Sony Xperia L4', 'manufacturer': 'Sony', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide) + 5 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie)'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei nova 7 5G', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 8 MP (telephoto) 3x optical zoom + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 (AOSP + HMS) + EMUI 10.1'}
{'device_name': 'Honor Play 9A', 'manufacturer': 'Honor', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP + 2 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 (AOSP + HMS) + Magic UI 3.0'}
{'device_name': 'Nokia 1.3', 'manufacturer': 'Nokia', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 (Go edition), planned upgrade to Android 11'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo A92s', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro ) + 2 MP depth sensor'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 + ColorOS 7.0'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei nova 7 Pro 5G', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + Periscope 8 MP (telephoto) 5x optical zoom + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)+ 8 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 (AOSP + HMS) + EMUI 10.1'}
{'device_name': 'Allview V4 Viper Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Allview', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP + 0.3 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Motorola Moto G Stylus', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 16 MP (ultrawide) dedicated video camera (1080p) + 5 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0'}
{'device_name': 'Realme 6 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'realme', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 12 MP (telephoto) 2x optical zoom + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP + 8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 + Realme UI'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy A41', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 5 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '25 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 + One UI 2'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Mi Note 10 Lite', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro) + 5 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 + MIUI 11'}
{'device_name': 'Coolpad Legacy 5G', 'manufacturer': 'Coolpad', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0'}
{'device_name': 'Realme X50m 5G', 'manufacturer': 'realme', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 + Realme UI'}
{'device_name': 'vivo Z6 5G', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 + Funtouch 10.0'}
{'device_name': 'vivo V19 (Indonesia)', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 + Funtouch 10.0'}
{'device_name': 'Realme C3 (3 cameras)', 'manufacturer': 'realme', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 + realme UI 1.0'}
{'device_name': 'Honor 8A 2020', 'manufacturer': 'Honor', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie) + EMUI 9'}
{'device_name': 'Cat S32', 'manufacturer': 'CAT', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, AF'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0, planned upgrade to Android 11.0'}
{'device_name': 'Realme 6', 'manufacturer': 'realme', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP B/W (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 + Realme UI'}
{'device_name': 'Motorola Moto E6s (2020)', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie)'}
{'device_name': 'LG W10 Alpha', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie)'}
{'device_name': 'Nokia C2', 'manufacturer': 'Nokia', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie (Go edition)'}
{'device_name': 'Realme C2s', 'manufacturer': 'realme', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide) + 2 MP depth sensor'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie) + ColorOS 6.1'}
{'device_name': 'LG K61', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro) + 5 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei P40 lite E', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP depth sensor'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie) (AOSP + HMS), EMUI 9.1'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo Reno Ace 2', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth) lenses'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10 + ColorOS 6.1'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy A11', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide) + 5 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0'}
{'device_name': 'LG V60 ThinQ 5G', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (standard) + 13 MP (ultrawide) + 0.3 MP TOF (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '10 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0'}
{'device_name': 'Motorola Edge', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 8 MP (telephoto), 3x optical zoom + 16 MP (ultrawide) + TOF 3D (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '25 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0'}
{'device_name': 'Honor 30 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Honor', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '40 MP (wide) + Periscope 8 MP (telephoto) 5x optical zoom + 16 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 (AOSP + HMS) + Magic UI 3.1'}
{'device_name': 'Infinix Note 7 Lite', 'manufacturer': 'Infinix', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth) + QVGA'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 + XOS 6.0'}
{'device_name': 'vivo Y50', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'Unknown selfie camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 + Funtouch 10.0'}
{'device_name': 'TCL 10L', 'manufacturer': 'TCL', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 + TCL UI'}
{'device_name': 'Infinix Note 7', 'manufacturer': 'Infinix', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth) + 2 MP (dedicated video camera)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 + XOS 6.0'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo Find X2 Lite', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP B/W + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 + ColorOS 7'}
{'device_name': 'Alcatel 3L (2020)', 'manufacturer': 'Alcatel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 5 MP (ultra-wide/depth sensor) + 2 MP (dedicated macro camera)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE nubia Red Magic 3s', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie) + Redmagic 2.0'}
{'device_name': 'Realme X2 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 13MP (telephoto) 2x optical zoom + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP depth sensor'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie), planned upgrade to Android 10.0; ColorOS 6.1'}
{'device_name': 'Realme C2 2020', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide) + 2 MP depth sensor'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie) + ColorOS 6 Lite'}
{'device_name': 'Honor 20 lite (China)', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP depth sensor'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie) + EMUI 9.1'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Mate 30 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '40 MP (wide) + 8 MP (telephoto) 3x optical zoom + 40 MP (ultrawide) + 3D TOF camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide) + 3D TOF camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10 + EMUI 10'}
{'device_name': 'Ulefone Armor 7', 'manufacturer': 'Ulefone', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48MP Main camera + 16MP night photography camera + 8MP telephoto camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Realme X50', 'manufacturer': 'realme', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 12 MP (telephoto) 2x optical zoom + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP dedicated macro camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 + ColorOS 7'}
{'device_name': 'Nokia 2.3', 'manufacturer': 'Nokia', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP + 2 MP depth sensor'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie) + planned upgrade to Android 10 + Android One'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Mate 30', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '40 MP (wide) + 8 MP (telephoto) 3x optical zoom + 16 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '24 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10 + EMUI 10'}
{'device_name': 'Sony Xperia 5 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Sony', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP (wide) predictive Dual Pixel PDAF, 5-axis OIS + 12 MP (telephoto) predictive PDAF, 2x optical zoom, 5-axis OIS + 12 MP (ultrawide) + 12 MP (ultrawide). Additionally, there is a TOF 3D camera.'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie)'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE Blade V20 (RUMORED)', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP + 8 MP + 2 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie) + MiFavor 9.0'}
{'device_name': 'Ulefone Armor 6S', 'manufacturer': 'Ulefone', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP + 8 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'vivo U20', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP macro camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie) + Funtouch 9.0'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei nova 6 SE', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (wide) dedicated macro camera + 2 MP depth sensor'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10 + EMUI 10'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy A91 (RUMORED)', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP + 12 MP + 5 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie) + One UI'}
{'device_name': 'Ulefone Armor X5', 'manufacturer': 'Ulefone', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP + 2 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Plum Tag 2 3G', 'manufacturer': 'Plum', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '1.3 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'No'}, 'operating_system': 'N/A'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Y6s (2019)', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie) + EMUI 9.1'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy A51', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 12 MP (ultrawide) + 5 MP (wide) dedicated macro camera + 5 MP depth sensor'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 + One UI 2'}
{'device_name': 'Doogee N20', 'manufacturer': 'Doogee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16.0MP+8.0MP+ 8.0MP f/2.0 130Â° Wide-angle LED Flash'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16.0MP 16.0MP f/2.0 80Â° Wide-angle'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Nova 6 5G', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '40 MP (wide) + 8 MP (telephoto) 3x optical zoom + 8 MP (ultrawide) lenses'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10 + EMUI 10'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Enjoy 10s', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP, f/1.8, 28mm (wide) PDAF + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP depth sensor'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie) + EMUI 9.1'}
{'device_name': 'alcatel 1v (2019)', 'manufacturer': 'Alcatel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie (Go edition)'}
{'device_name': 'Realme 5i', 'manufacturer': 'realme', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultra-wide) + 2 MP (dedicated macro camera) + 2 MP depth sensor'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie), planned upgrade to Android 10.0; ColorOS 6'}
{'device_name': 'vivo iQOO Neo 855 Racing', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP dual pixel PDAF + 8 MP (wide) + 2 MP depth sensor '}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie) + Funtouch 9'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Y9s', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (depth sensor)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'Motorized pop-up 16 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie) + EMUI 9.1'}
{'device_name': 'vivo iQOO Neo 855', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP dual pixel PDAF + 8 MP (wide) + 2 MP depth sensor '}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie) + Funtouch 9'}
{'device_name': 'Doogee S95 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Doogee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP + 2 MP + 8 MP (depth sensor) + 8 MP (ultrawide angle)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'alcatel 3x (2019)', 'manufacturer': 'Alcatel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 5 MP depth sensor'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie)'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo F15', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultra-wide) + 2 MP B/W + 2 MP depth sensor'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie) + ColorOS 6.1'}
{'device_name': 'vivo Y9s', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (dedicated macro camera) + 2 MP depth sensor'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie) + Funtouch 9'}
{'device_name': 'Oukitel K7 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Oukitel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP + 5 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Doogee N100', 'manufacturer': 'Doogee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '21 MP + 2 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Coolpad Cool 5', 'manufacturer': 'Coolpad', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP + 2 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie)'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE Blade 10 Prime', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP + 5 MP depth sensor'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie)'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy Note10 Lite', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP (wide) + 12 MP (telephoto) 2x optical zoom + 12 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 + One UI 2'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo A11', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP + 2 MP depth sensor'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie) + ColorOS 6.0'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy A70s', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 5 MP depth sensor'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie) + One UI'}
{'device_name': 'Motorola Moto E6 Play', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie)'}
{'device_name': 'Sharp S7 Android One', 'manufacturer': 'Sharp', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP + 2 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android One (Android 10)'}
{'device_name': 'Orange Neva jet 5G', 'manufacturer': 'Unknown', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'N/A'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'N/A'}, 'operating_system': 'N/A'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo A11x', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP + 8 MP + 2 MP + 2 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie) + ColorOS 6.0.1'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE Blade A7 Prime', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie)'}
{'device_name': 'Nokia 2720 Flip', 'manufacturer': 'Nokia', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '2 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'No'}, 'operating_system': 'KaiOS'}
{'device_name': 'BLU Bold N1', 'manufacturer': 'BLU', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP + 5 MP (depth sensor)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'Motorized pop-up 13 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie), planned upgrade to Android 10.0'}
{'device_name': 'Meizu M10', 'manufacturer': 'Meizu', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide) + 2 MP + 2 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie) + Flyme 8'}
{'device_name': 'Meizu 16T', 'manufacturer': 'Meizu', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 5 MP (wide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie) + Flyme 8'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo A8', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro camera) + 2 MP depth sensor'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie) + ColorOS 6.1'}
{'device_name': 'Motorola Moto One Macro', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP + 2 MP + 2 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie)'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Redmi 8A', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP dual pixel PDAF'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie) + MIUI 10'}
{'device_name': 'vivo S5', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (dedicated macro camera) + 5 MP depth sensor cameras'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie); Funtouch 9.2'}
{'device_name': 'TECNO Pop 2 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Tecno', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo (Go edition)'}
{'device_name': 'Ulefone Armor 3WT', 'manufacturer': 'Ulefone', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '21 MP Camera Sony IMX230'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP Camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Cubot R15 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Cubot', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP + 2 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy Xcover Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 + One UI 2'}
{'device_name': 'vivo Y3 Standard', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide) + 2 MP depth sensor'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie) + Funtouch 9.1'}
{'device_name': 'Google Pixel 4', 'manufacturer': 'Google', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.2 MP (wide) + 16 MP (telephoto) 2x optical zoom'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (ultrawide) + TOF 3D camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10'}
{'device_name': 'Infinix Smart 4c', 'manufacturer': 'Infinix', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP + QVGA'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie)'}
{'device_name': 'Ulefone Armor 3W', 'manufacturer': 'Ulefone', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '21 MP Camera Sony IMX230'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP Camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'BLU C6 2019', 'manufacturer': 'BLU', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo (Go edition)'}
{'device_name': 'Cubot P30', 'manufacturer': 'Cubot', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP + 20 MP + 8 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'TECNO Pop 2 F', 'manufacturer': 'Tecno', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 (Oreo) + HIOS 4.1'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo A91', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (dedicated macro camera) + 2 MP depth sensor'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie)'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Redmi Note 8T', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (dedicated macro camera) + 2 MP depth sensor lenses'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie) + MIUI 10'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo K5', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (dedicated macro camera) + 2 MP depth sensor'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie) + planned upgrade to Android 10.0 + ColorOS 6'}
{'device_name': 'TECNO Pouvoir 3', 'manufacturer': 'Tecno', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 (Oreo) + HIOS 4.1'}
{'device_name': 'Ulefone Armor X3', 'manufacturer': 'Ulefone', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP+2 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'OnePlus 7T Pro 5G McLaren', 'manufacturer': 'Oneplus', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (telephoto) 3x optical zoom + 16 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'Motorized pop-up 16 MP, f/2.0, 25mm (wide), 1/3.1, 1.0Âµm'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 + OxygenOS 10.0'}
{'device_name': 'vivo Z5i', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP macro camera lenses'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie) + Funtouch 9.2'}
{'device_name': 'Google Pixel 4 XL', 'manufacturer': 'Google', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.2 MP (wide) + 16 MP (telephoto) 2x optical zoom'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (ultrawide) + TOF 3D camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10'}
{'device_name': 'LG V50S ThinQ 5G', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP (standard) Dual Pixel PDAF + 13 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei P smart Pro 2019', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (depth sensor)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'Motorized pop-up 16 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie) + EMUI 9.1'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Mi Note 10 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '108 MP (7P lens) (wide) + 12 MP (telephoto)  2x optical zoom + 5 MP (upscaled to 8MP) (telephoto) 5x optical zoom + 20 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (dedicated macro camera)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie) + MIUI 11'}
{'device_name': 'TECNO Pouvoir 3 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Tecno', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie) + HIOS 5.0'}
{'device_name': 'Honor V30 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '40 MP (wide) + 8 MP (telephoto) 3x optical zoom + 12 MP (ultrawide) lenses'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) sensor'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 + Magic UI 3'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo Reno 2', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 13 MP (telephoto) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP B/W'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10 + ColorOS 6.1'}
{'device_name': 'TECNO Pouvoir 3 Air', 'manufacturer': 'Tecno', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie (Go edition) + HIOS 5.0'}
{'device_name': 'vivo Y11 (2019)', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP + 2 MP depth sensor'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie) + Funtouch 9.1'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy A01', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide) AF + 2 MP depth sensor'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 + One UI 2'}
{'device_name': 'Oukitel Y1000', 'manufacturer': 'Oukitel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP + 2 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Nokia 3 V', 'manufacturer': 'Nokia', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie), upgradable to Android 10, Android One'}
{'device_name': 'HTC Exodus 1s', 'manufacturer': 'HTC', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 (Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Mi Mix Alpha', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '108 MP (wide) + 12 MP (telephoto) Dual Pixel PDAF, Laser AF, 2x optical zoom + 20 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'No - uses main camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10 + MIUI 11'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Mate 30 5G', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '40 MP (wide) + 8 MP (telephoto) 3x optical zoom + 16 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '24 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10 + EMUI 10'}
{'device_name': 'TECNO Camon 12', 'manufacturer': 'Tecno', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP + 8 MP + 2 MP depth sensor'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie) + HIOS 5.5'}
{'device_name': 'Motorola One Hyper', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'Motorized pop-up 32 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10 + Android One'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Mi 9 Pro 5G', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 12 MP (telephoto) 2x optical zoom + 16 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '20MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10 + MIUI 11'}
{'device_name': 'vivo U3', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP macro camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie) + Funtouch 9.0'}
{'device_name': 'TECNO Camon 12 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Tecno', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP + 8 MP + 2 MP depth sensor'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie) + HIOS 5.5'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy S10 Lite', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 12 MP (ultrawide) + 5 MP dedicated macro camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 + One UI 2'}
{'device_name': 'Gigaset GX290', 'manufacturer': 'Gigaset', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP AF (SONY sensor) + 2 MP dual rear camera with ArcSoftR solution'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP with LED Flash Light'}, 'operating_system': 'Pure Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo X30 Pro 5G', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) PDAF Laser AF OIS + Periscope 13 MP (telephoto) 5x optical zoom + 32 MP (telephoto) PDAF, Laser AF, OIS, 2x optical zoom + 8 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie) + Funtouch 10.0'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei nova 5z', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (wide) dedicated macro camera + 2 MP depth sensor'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie) + EMUI 9.1'}
{'device_name': 'BLU Studio Mega 2019', 'manufacturer': 'BLU', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie)'}
{'device_name': 'Sharp Aquos V', 'manufacturer': 'Sharp', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP OIS + 13 MP B/W'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie)'}
{'device_name': 'Gigaset GS195', 'manufacturer': 'Gigaset', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP + 5 MP dual'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP with LED Flash Light'}, 'operating_system': 'Pure Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE Axon 10s Pro 5G', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (telephoto) 3x optical zoom + 20 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '20 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 + MiFavor 10'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Mi 9 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 12 MP (telephoto) 2x optical zoom + 16 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '20MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10 + MIUI 11'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Mate 30 Pro 5G', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '40 MP (wide) + 8 MP (telephoto) + 40 MP (ultrawide) + 3D TOF camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP, (wide) + 3D TOF camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10 + EMUI 10'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo Reno3 5G', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '60 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP B/W + 2 MP depth sensor'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 + ColorOS 7'}
{'device_name': 'BLU G9 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'BLU', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP + 20 MP (wide) + 5 MP depth sensor'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '24 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie), planned upgrade to Android 10.0'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei nova 6', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '40 MP (wide) + 8 MP (telephoto) 3x optical zoom + 8 MP (ultrawide) lenses'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10 + EMUI 10'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo S1 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (dedicated macro camera) + 2 MP depth sensor'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie) + Funtouch 9.2'}
{'device_name': 'vivo U10', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP depth sensor'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie) + Funtouch 9.1'}
{'device_name': 'BLU Vivo XL5', 'manufacturer': 'BLU', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP + 2MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie)'}
{'device_name': 'Honor V30', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '40 MP (wide) + 8 MP (telephoto) 3x optical zoom + 8 MP (ultrawide) lenses'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) sensor'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 + Magic UI 3'}
{'device_name': 'vivo Y19', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP macro camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie) + Funtouch 9.2'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo X30 5G', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) PDAF Laser AF OIS + 32 MP (telephoto) PDAF, Laser AF, OIS, 2x optical zoom + 8 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie) + Funtouch 10.0'}
{'device_name': 'BLU Vivo X5', 'manufacturer': 'BLU', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, AF'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie)'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE Blade 20', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP depth sensor'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie)'}
{'device_name': 'Gigaset GS190', 'manufacturer': 'Gigaset', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Pure Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'UMIDIGI F2', 'manufacturer': 'UMiDigi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 48MP primary camera, Samsung GM1, 1/2'' image sensor 6-element lens + 13MP ultra wide angle camera, FOV 120Â° + 5MP depth camera 5MP macro camera, 2cm macro distance}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP 5-element lens'}, 'operating_system': 'Latest Stock Android 10 + System-Wide Dark Theme'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei P smart 2020', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP + 2 (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie) + EMUI 9.1, Google Play Services'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo A5 (2020)', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP + 2 MP depth sensor'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie) + ColorOS 6.0'}
{'device_name': 'Realme 5s', 'manufacturer': 'realme', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (dedicated macro camera) + 2 MP depth sensor'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie) + ColorOS 6'}
{'device_name': 'Cat S52', 'manufacturer': 'CAT', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP (wide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie), planned upgrade to Android 10.0'}
{'device_name': 'Realme X2', 'manufacturer': 'realme', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (dedicated macro camera) + 2 MP depth sensor'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie), planned upgrade to Android 10.0 + ColorOS 6'}
{'device_name': 'Gionee F9 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Gionee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP + 2 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'BLU Studio Mini', 'manufacturer': 'BLU', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, AF'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie)'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Mate 30 Lite (RUMORED)', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (wide) dedicated macro camera + 2 MP depth sensor'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie) + EMUI 9.1'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy A71', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 12 MP (ultrawide) + 5 MP (wide) dedicated macro camera + 5 MP depth sensor'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 + One UI 2'}
{'device_name': 'OnePlus 8 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Oneplus', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) omnidirectional + 48 MP (ultrawide) + 8MP telephoto lens + 5MP color filter (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 + OxygenOS 10.0'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Mi Note 10', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '108 MP (7P lens) (wide) + 12 MP (telephoto)  2x optical zoom + 5 MP (upscaled to 8MP) (telephoto) 5x optical zoom + 20 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (dedicated macro camera)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie) + MIUI 11'}
{'device_name': 'Energizer Ultimate U650S', 'manufacturer': 'Energizer', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP + 2 MP depth sensor'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie)'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Mi CC9 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '108 MP (wide) PDAF, Laser AF + 12 MP (telephoto) Dual Pixel PDAF, Laser AF, 2x optical zoom + 20 MP (ultrawide) Laser AF + 2 MP (dedicated macro camera) cameras'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie) + MIUI 11'}
{'device_name': 'Motorola Moto G8 Play (RUMORED)', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 16 MP (ultrawide) dedicated video camera (1080p) + 5 MP depth sensor'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '25 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie)'}
{'device_name': 'Lenovo K10 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Lenovo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 5 MP depth sensor'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie) + ZUI 11'}
{'device_name': 'Blackview BV9800', 'manufacturer': 'Blackview', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Nokia C1', 'manufacturer': 'Nokia', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie (Go edition)'}
{'device_name': 'HTC Desire 19s', 'manufacturer': 'HTC', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide) + 5 MP (ultrawide) + 5 MP depth sensor'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9 (Pie)'}
{'device_name': 'Energizer Power Max P8100S', 'manufacturer': 'Energizer', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP + 12 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '24 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie)'}
{'device_name': 'Energizer Hardcase H10', 'manufacturer': 'Energizer', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'VGA'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'VGA'}, 'operating_system': 'N/A'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Redmi K20 Pro Premium', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (telephoto) 2x optical zoom + 13 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'Motorized pop-up 20 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10; MIUI 11'}
{'device_name': 'vivo V17', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (dedicated macro camera) + 2 MP depth sensor'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie) + Funtouch 9.2'}
{'device_name': 'Honor Play 3e', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, f/2.2'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie) + EMUI 9.1'}
{'device_name': 'Blackview BV9800 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Blackview', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy Xcover FieldPro', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie)'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Mate 30 RS Porsche Design', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '40 MP (wide) + 8 MP (telephoto) 3x optical zoom + 40 MP (ultrawide) + 3D TOF camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide) + 3D TOF camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10 + EMUI 10'}
{'device_name': 'Energizer Energy E12', 'manufacturer': 'Energizer', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'VGA'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'VGA'}, 'operating_system': 'N/A'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo Reno3 Pro 5G', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 13 MP (telephoto) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP depth sensor'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 + ColorOS 7'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Enjoy 10', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 2 MP depth sensor'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie) + EMUI 9.1'}
{'device_name': 'Motorola Razr 2019', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP + TOF 3D (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Motorola Moto G8 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 16 MP (ultrawide) dedicated video camera (1080p) + 5 MP depth sensor'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '25 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie)'}
{'device_name': 'Doogee S68 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Doogee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'Sony 21 MP + 8 MP + 8 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'vivo V17 (India)', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (dedicated macro camera) + 2 MP depth sensor'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie) + Funtouch 9.2'}
{'device_name': 'Doogee S40 Lite', 'manufacturer': 'Doogee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP + 5 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'OnePlus 7T Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Oneplus', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (telephoto) 3x optical zoom + 16 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'Motorized pop-up 16 MP, f/2.0, 25mm (wide), 1/3.1, 1.0Âµm'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 + OxygenOS 10.0'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Redmi K30', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (dedicated macro camera) + 2 MP depth sensor'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '20 MP (wide) + 2 MP depth sensor'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10 + MIUI 11'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Redmi K30 5G', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (dedicated macro camera) + 2 MP depth sensor'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '20 MP (wide) + 2 MP depth sensor'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10 + MIUI 11'}
{'device_name': 'Infinix S5', 'manufacturer': 'Infinix', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide) + 5 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP depth sensor'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie)'}
{'device_name': 'vivo NEX 3', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 13 MP (telephoto) + 13 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'Motorized pop-up 16 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie) + Funtouch 9.1'}
{'device_name': 'Realme XT 730G (RUMORED)', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (dedicated macro camera) + 2 MP depth sensor'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie), planned upgrade to Android 10.0 + ColorOS 6'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy M10s', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide) + 5 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie)'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo A9 (2020)', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP + 2 MP depth sensor'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie) + ColorOS 6.1'}
{'device_name': 'Infinix Hot 8', 'manufacturer': 'Infinix', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide) + 2 MP, depth sensor + QVGA (Low light sensor) lenses'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie) + XOS 5.0'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy A20s', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 5 MP depth sensor'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie)'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo V17 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 13mm (ultrawide) + 2 MP + 2 MP,  depth sensor'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP + 8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie) + Funtouch 9.1'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy Tab Active Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie)'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy Fold 5G', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP (wide) + 12 MP (telephoto) + 16 MP (ultrawide) lenses'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '10 MP (wide) + 8 MP (wide), depth sensor'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie)'}
{'device_name': 'Hotwav Pearl K1', 'manufacturer': 'Haier', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Apple iPhone 11 Pro Max', 'manufacturer': 'Apple', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP (wide) + 12 MP (telephoto) + 12 MP (ultrawide) cameras'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP + TOF 3D camera'}, 'operating_system': 'iOS 13'}
{'device_name': 'LG W30 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP, PDAF'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie)'}
{'device_name': 'HTC Wildfire X', 'manufacturer': 'HTC', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP, (wide) + 8 MP, (telephoto) + 5 MP, depth sensor'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9 (Pie)'}
{'device_name': 'Elephone A6 Max', 'manufacturer': 'Elephone', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '20.1 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '20.1 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'UMIDIGI X', 'manufacturer': 'UMiDigi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'LG W30', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, PDAF'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie)'}
{'device_name': 'Apple iPhone 11 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Apple', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP (wide) + 12 MP (telephoto) + 12 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP + TOF 3D camera'}, 'operating_system': 'iOS 13'}
{'device_name': 'Hotwav M6', 'manufacturer': 'Haier', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Walton Primo H8 Turbo', 'manufacturer': 'Walton', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'vivo iQOO Pro 5G', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 13 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP depth sensor'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie) + Funtouch 9.1'}
{'device_name': 'vivo NEX 3 5G', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 13 MP (telephoto) + 13 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'Motorized pop-up 16 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie) + Funtouch 9.1'}
{'device_name': 'LG W10', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, PDAF'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie)'}
{'device_name': 'Apple iPhone 11', 'manufacturer': 'Apple', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP (wide) + 12 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP + TOF 3D camera'}, 'operating_system': 'iOS 13'}
{'device_name': 'Wiko Y70', 'manufacturer': 'Wiko', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Gionee F9', 'manufacturer': 'Gionee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'DEXP AL240', 'manufacturer': 'DEXP', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '0.31 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei nova 5 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP, PDAF'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie)'}
{'device_name': 'Doogee S90 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Doogee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'OnePlus 7T', 'manufacturer': 'Oneplus', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 12 MP (telephoto) 2x optical zoom + 16 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0; OxygenOS 10'}
{'device_name': 'Meizu 16s Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Meizu', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP, f/1.7, (wide), 1/2, 0.8Âµm, PDAF, OIS + 20MP, f/2.6, (telephoto), 1/2.8, 1.0Âµm, PDAF + 16 MP, f/2.2, 16mm (ultrawide), 1/3.6, 1.0Âµm'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '20MP, f/2.2'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Mi CC9 Meitu Edition', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '31.96 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'MIUI V10.2 (Android 9.0 Pie)'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Mi CC9e', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP, f/1.8, 27mm (wide), 1/2, 0.8Âµm, PDAF'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie); MIUI 10'}
{'device_name': 'LG G8X ThinQ', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP (standard) Dual Pixel PDAF + 13 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP, f/1.9, 26mm (wide), 0.8Âµm'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie)'}
{'device_name': 'LG Q70', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP, f/1.8, (wide), PDAF + 13 MP, f/2.2, 13mm (ultrawide)+ 5 MP, f/2.4, depth sensor'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie); LG UX 7'}
{'device_name': 'LG G8s ThinQ', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.19 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8.07 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Ðreo'}
{'device_name': 'AGM X3 JBL', 'manufacturer': 'AGM', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.19 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '19.66 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'X OS 3.0 (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Honor 9X Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (1080p) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (depth sensor)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'Motorized pop-up 16 MP, f/2.0'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie)'}
{'device_name': 'BQ Mobile BQ-5535L Strike Power Plus', 'manufacturer': 'BQ Mobile', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'vivo iQOO Neo', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP, f/1.8, 1/2.55, 1.4Âµm, dual pixel PDAF'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP, f/2.0'}, 'operating_system': 'Funtouch 9.0 OS (Android 9.0 Pie)'}
{'device_name': 'Nokia 800 Tough', 'manufacturer': 'Nokia', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '2 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'No'}, 'operating_system': 'KaiOS'}
{'device_name': 'Symphony V141', 'manufacturer': 'Symphony', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Symphony i18', 'manufacturer': 'Symphony', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Redmi Note 8', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (dedicated macro camera) + 2 MP depth sensor lenses'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie); MIUI 10'}
{'device_name': 'BQ Mobile BQ-6035L Strike Power Max', 'manufacturer': 'BQ Mobile', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Nomu T20', 'manufacturer': 'Nomu', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'vivo Z5', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP, f/1.8, (wide), 1/2, 0.8Âµm, PDAF | 8 MP, f/2.2, 13mm (ultrawide) | 5 MP, f/2.4, depth sensor'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP, f/2.0'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie)'}
{'device_name': 'Honor 9X', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (depth sensor)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'Motorized pop-up 16 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie) + EMUI 9.1'}
{'device_name': 'E&L D63', 'manufacturer': 'EL', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy A90 5G', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 5 MP depth sensor'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP, f/2.0'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie); One UI'}
{'device_name': 'Realme XT', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (dedicated macro camera) + 2 MP depth sensor'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie), planned upgrade to Android 10.0 + ColorOS 6'}
{'device_name': 'alcatel TCL Plex', 'manufacturer': 'Alcatel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 16 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '24 MP, f/2.0, 26mm (wide), 1/2.8, 0.9Î¼m'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie)'}
{'device_name': 'Vernee X2', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie); Android One'}
{'device_name': 'Texet TM-5583 Pay 5.5', 'manufacturer': 'Texet', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Asus ROG Phone 2', 'manufacturer': 'ASUS', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP, f/1.8, 26mm (wide), 1/2, 0.8Âµm, PDAF/Laser AF'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '24MP, f/2.2'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie)'}
{'device_name': 'Motorola One Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP, f/1.6, (wide), 1/2, 0.8Âµm, PDAF'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '25 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie); Android One'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Redmi Note 8 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (dedicated macro camera) + 2 MP depth sensor lenses'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '20 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie); MIUI 10'}
{'device_name': 'Nokia 7.2', 'manufacturer': 'Nokia', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 5 MP, depth sensor'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '20 MP, f/2.0'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie) + Android One'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE nubia Z20', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP, f/1.6, 26mm (wide), 1/2, 0.8Âµm, PDAF'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie)'}
{'device_name': 'E&L D62', 'manufacturer': 'EL', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'vivo Z1 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP, f/1.8, (wide), AF'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP, f/2.0'}, 'operating_system': 'Funtouch 9.0 OS (Android 9.0 Pie)'}
{'device_name': 'Walton Primo NH4', 'manufacturer': 'Walton', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'E&L D58', 'manufacturer': 'EL', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '6.18 in (inches)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy A10s', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide), AF + 2 MP depth sensor'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, f/2.0'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo Reno2 Z', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP, f/1.7, 26mm (wide), 1/2.0, 0.8Âµm, PDAF, OIS + 8 MP, f/2.2, 16mm (ultrawide), 1/3.2 + 2 MP B/W + 2 MP, depth sensor'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'Motorized pop-up 16 MP, f/2.0, 26mm (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie)'}
{'device_name': 'Sony Xperia 5', 'manufacturer': 'Sony', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP (wide) predictive Dual Pixel PDAF, 5-axis OIS + 12 MP (telephoto), predictive PDAF, 2x optical zoom, 5-axis OIS + 12 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, f/2.0, 24mm (wide), 1/4, 1.12Âµm'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie)'}
{'device_name': 'Motorola One Action', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.6 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 5 MP depth sensor'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '12.6 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie); Android One'}
{'device_name': 'E&L D57', 'manufacturer': 'EL', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '6.18 in (inches)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'DEXP A240', 'manufacturer': 'DEXP', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '0.31 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Mi A3', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP, f/1.8, (wide), 1/2, 0.8Âµm, PDAF'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP, f/2.0, 0.8Âµm'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie); Android One'}
{'device_name': 'Walton Primo R6 Max', 'manufacturer': 'Walton', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'E&L 6P', 'manufacturer': 'EL', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '6.18 in (inches)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Blackview BV9100', 'manufacturer': 'Blackview', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Motorola One Zoom', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (telephoto), 3x optical zoom, OIS + 16 MP (ultrawide) + 5 MP, depth sensor'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '25 MP, f/2.0, 0.9Âµm'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie) + Android One'}
{'device_name': 'Texet TM-5084', 'manufacturer': 'Texet', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'BLU G5', 'manufacturer': 'BLU', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Mi 9T', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP, f/1.8, 27mm (wide), 1/2, 0.8Âµm, PDAF'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'Motorized pop-up 20 MP, f/2.2, 0.8Âµm'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie); MIUI 10'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Mi 9T Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP, f/1.8, 26mm (wide) + 8 MP, f/2.4, 53mm (telephoto) + 13 MP, f/2.4, 12mm (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'Motorized pop-up 20 MP, f/2.2, 0.8Âµm'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie); MIUI 10'}
{'device_name': 'E&L 6C', 'manufacturer': 'EL', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo Reno A', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP + 2 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '25 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie) + ColorOS 6'}
{'device_name': 'Nubia Red Magic 3S', 'manufacturer': 'Nubia', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 megapixel + Self-portrait beauty support'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 + Redmagic OS 2.1'}
{'device_name': 'Noa N3', 'manufacturer': 'Noa', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'LG Stylo 5', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, PDAF'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Nokia 6.2', 'manufacturer': 'Nokia', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 5 MP, depth sensor'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie) + Android One'}
{'device_name': 'Nokia 3.1 A', 'manufacturer': 'Nokia', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, f/2.0, AF'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, f/2.2'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie)'}
{'device_name': 'vivo iQOO Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP, f/1.8, (wide), 1/2, 0.8Âµm, PDAF + 13 MP, f/2.2, (ultrawide) + 2 MP, f/2.4, depth sensor'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP, f/2.0'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie); Funtouch 9.1'}
{'device_name': 'Lenovo Z6', 'manufacturer': 'Lenovo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '24 MP, f/1.8, (wide), 1.8Âµm, PDAF'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'HiSense Infinity H30', 'manufacturer': 'Hisense', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '19.96 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'BLU G5 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'BLU', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Honor 20S', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP depth sensor'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP, f/2.0, 0.8Âµm'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie); Magic 2.1'}
{'device_name': 'HiSense Infinity H30 Lite', 'manufacturer': 'Hisense', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy Note 10 Plus 5G', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP, f/1.5-1.8-2.4, 27mm (wide) + 12 MP, f/2.1, 52mm (telephoto) + 16 MP, f/2.2, 12mm (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '10 MP, f/1.6, 26mm (wide), 1.22Âµm, Dual Pixel PDAF'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie); One UI'}
{'device_name': 'Texet TM-5584', 'manufacturer': 'Texet', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Walton Primo S7', 'manufacturer': 'Walton', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.19 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Motorola Moto E6 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP + 2 MP depth sensor'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, f/2.0, 1.12Âµm'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie)'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy A50s', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP, f/2.0, (wide), 1/2, 0.8Âµm, PDAF + 8 MP, f/2.2, 13mm (ultrawide) + 5 MP, f/2.2, depth sensor'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP, f/2.0, 25mm (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy Note 10 5G', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP, f/1.5-1.8-2.4, 27mm (wide) + 12 MP, f/2.1, 52mm (telephoto) + 16 MP, f/2.2, 12mm (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '10 MP, f/2.2, 26mm (wide), 1.22Âµm, Dual Pixel PDAF'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie); One UI'}
{'device_name': 'Google Pixel 3a', 'manufacturer': 'Google', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.2 MP, f/1.8, 28mm (wide), 1/2.55, 1.4Âµm, dual pixel PDAF, OIS'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, f/2.0, 24mm (wide), 1.12Âµm'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie)'}
{'device_name': 'BLU G6', 'manufacturer': 'BLU', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Realme 3i', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie); ColorOS 6'}
{'device_name': 'Honor Play 3', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP depth sensor'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, f/2.0'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie), EMUI 9.1'}
{'device_name': 'Ulefone Power 6', 'manufacturer': 'Ulefone', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy Note 10', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP, f/1.5-1.8-2.4, 27mm (wide) + 12 MP, f/2.1, 52mm (telephoto) + 16 MP, f/2.2, 12mm (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '10 MP, f/2.2, 26mm (wide), 1.22Âµm, Dual Pixel PDAF'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie); One UI'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy A30s', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '25 MP, f/1.7, PDAF + 8 MP, f/2.2, 13mm (ultrawide) + 5 MP, f/2.2, depth sensor'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP, f/2.0'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Ulefone Note 7P', 'manufacturer': 'Ulefone', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': '10.or G2', 'manufacturer': '360', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '12.19 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo Reno2 F', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP B/W + 2 MP depth sensor'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'Motorized pop-up 16 MP, f/2.0, 26mm (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie); ColorOS 6.1'}
{'device_name': 'TECNO Phantom 9', 'manufacturer': 'Tecno', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP, f/1.8, PDAF'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP, f/2.0'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie)'}
{'device_name': 'HTC U19e', 'manufacturer': 'HTC', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP, f/1.8, 26mm (wide), PDAF 20 MP, f/2.6, 52mm (telephoto)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '24 MP, f/2.0'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie); HTC Sense'}
{'device_name': 'Pluzz PL5014', 'manufacturer': 'Pluzz', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'LG K50S', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/2.2, 26mm (wide), PDAF + 5 MP, (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/2.0'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie)'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Enjoy 10 Plus (RUMORED)', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP depth sensor'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'Motorized pop-up 16 MP, f/2.0'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie), EMUI 9.1'}
{'device_name': 'HTC Desire 19 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'HTC', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/2.0, 26mm (wide), PDAF'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP, f/2.0'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9 (Pie)'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei nova 5i Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP, f/1.8, 26mm (wide), 1/2, 0.8Âµm, PDAF, 8 MP, (ultrawide), 2 MP, f/2.4, 27mm (wide) dedicated macro camera, and 2 MP, f/2.4, depth sensor'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP, f/2.0'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie)'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Mi CC9', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP, f/1.8, 27mm (wide), 1/2, 0.8Âµm, PDAF'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie); MIUI 10'}
{'device_name': 'Pluzz Elite Dual', 'manufacturer': 'Pluzz', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'vivo Z1x (RUMORED)', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 5 MP depth sensor'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP, f/2.0'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie); Funtouch 9.1'}
{'device_name': 'BLU G8', 'manufacturer': 'BLU', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'LG K40S', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/2.2, 26mm (wide), PDAF + 5 MP, (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/2.0'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie)'}
{'device_name': 'Panasonic Eluga I7 (2019)', 'manufacturer': 'Panasonic', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, f/2.0, 1.12 Âµm'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, f/2.0, 1.12 Âµm, AF'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie)'}
{'device_name': 'Pluzz PL5016', 'manufacturer': 'Pluzz', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'N.A.'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'N.A.'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Wiko Jerry 4', 'manufacturer': 'Wiko', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE Nubia Red Magic 3', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels with CMOS Sensor, f2.0 Aperture, 1080p Video, Pixel size - 2.0 Î¼m'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie with Nubia Red Magic 2.0 UI'}
{'device_name': 'T-Mobile Revvlry', 'manufacturer': 'THL', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/2.0, 1.12Âµm, PDAF'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, f/2.2, 1.12Âµm'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie)'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei nova 5T', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP, f/1.8, 28mm (wide), 1/2, 0.8Âµm, PDAF + 16 MP, f/2.2, 13mm (ultrawide), 1/3.1 + 2 MP, f/2.4, 27mm (wide), dedicated macro camera + 2 MP, f/2.4, depth sensor'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP, f/2.0, 0.8Âµm'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie)'}
{'device_name': 'Wiko Y50', 'manufacturer': 'Wiko', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Lenovo K10 Note', 'manufacturer': 'Lenovo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP + 8 MP (telephoto) 2x optical zoom + 2 MP depth sensor'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie) + ZUI 11'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE nubia X 5G', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP, f/1.8, PDAF'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'Uses main cameras'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie)'}
{'device_name': 'Realme 5 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'realme', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP, f/1.8, (wide), 1/2, 0.8Âµm, PDAF + 8 MP, f/2.2, 13mm (ultrawide) + 2 MP, f/2.4 (dedicated macro camera) + 2 MP, f/2.4, depth sensor'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP, f/2.0'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie); ColorOS 6'}
{'device_name': 'T-Mobile Revvlry Plus', 'manufacturer': 'THL', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP, f/1.7, 1.22Âµm, PDAF, OIS'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP, 1.25Âµm'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie)'}
{'device_name': 'Oukitel C17 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Oukitel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Lava Z51', 'manufacturer': 'Lava', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Star OS 5.0 Lite (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Irbis SP542', 'manufacturer': 'Irbis', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Black Shark 2 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP, f/1.8, (wide), 1/2, 0.8Âµm, PDAF / 12 MP, f/2.2, (telephoto), 1.0Âµm, PDAF, 2x optical zoom'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '20 MP, f/2.0, 0.9Âµm'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie)'}
{'device_name': 'Lenovo Z6 Pro 5G', 'manufacturer': 'Lenovo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '31.96 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy Note 10 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP, f/1.5-1.8-2.4, 27mm (wide) + 12 MP, f/2.1, 52mm (telephoto) + 16 MP, f/2.2, 12mm (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '10 MP, f/1.6, 26mm (wide), 1.22Âµm, Dual Pixel PDAF'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie); One UI'}
{'device_name': 'Lenovo A6 Note', 'manufacturer': 'Lenovo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP + 2 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'InFocus A1s', 'manufacturer': 'Infocus', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Walton Primo Ef9', 'manufacturer': 'Walton', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Meizu 16th Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Meizu', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.19 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '19.66 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'FlyMe (Android 8.0 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Realme 5', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP, f/1.8, (wide), PDAF + 8 MP, f/2.2, 13mm (ultrawide) + 2 MP, f/2.4 (dedicated macro camera) + 2 MP, f/2.4, depth sensor'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'ColorOS 6.0 (Android 9.0 Pie)'}
{'device_name': 'Infinix Note 6', 'manufacturer': 'Infinix', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide), PDAF'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie)'}
{'device_name': 'Oukitel C16 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Oukitel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Coolpad Cool 3 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Coolpad', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, AF'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie)'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy M30s', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 5 MP depth sensor'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP, f/2.0'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie); One UI'}
{'device_name': 'Meizu 16th', 'manufacturer': 'Meizu', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.19 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '19.66 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'FlyMe (Android 8.0 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Maimang 8', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '23.79 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Redmi 8', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP + 2 MP depth sensor'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie) + MIUI 9'}
{'device_name': 'Blackview BV6100', 'manufacturer': 'Blackview', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'AllCall S10', 'manufacturer': 'AllCall', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels + 2 Megapixels (Dual Camera)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE nubia Z18', 'manufacturer': 'Nubia', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '24 MP, f/1.6, dual pixel PDAF, OIS'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, f/2.0'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 (Oreo); nubia UI 6'}
{'device_name': 'Irbis SP494', 'manufacturer': 'Irbis', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo Reno', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP + 13MP + 8 MP + 2 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'Motorized pop-up 16 MP, f/2.0, 26mm (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie)'}
{'device_name': 'M-Horse M1', 'manufacturer': 'M-Horse', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Blackview BV9600', 'manufacturer': 'Blackview', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Walton Primo NF4 Turbo', 'manufacturer': 'Walton', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Cubot X20 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Cubot', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'Main rear camera - 12MP + Secondary rear camera - 20MP + Third rear camera - 8MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'N.A.'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Blackview BV9500 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Blackview', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Walton Primo F9', 'manufacturer': 'Walton', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'TP-LINK Neffos X20 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'TP-LINK', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'TP-LINK Neffos X20', 'manufacturer': 'TP-LINK', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Gome C7 Note', 'manufacturer': 'Gome', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Gome OS 3.0 (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Gome C7', 'manufacturer': 'Gome', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Gome OS 3.0 (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Nokia 220 4G', 'manufacturer': 'Nokia', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '0.31 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'No'}, 'operating_system': 'Feature'}
{'device_name': 'Nokia 105 (2019)', 'manufacturer': 'Nokia', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'No'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'No'}, 'operating_system': 'Nokia Series 30+'}
{'device_name': 'Xgody Mate 20', 'manufacturer': 'Xtouch', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Gigaset GS110', 'manufacturer': 'Gigaset', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Pure Androidâ¢ 9.0 Pie - Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'TP-LINK Neffos C7s', 'manufacturer': 'TP-LINK', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Prestigio Muze J5', 'manufacturer': 'Prestigio', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Hotwav Pearl K2', 'manufacturer': 'Haier', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Xgody P30', 'manufacturer': 'Xtouch', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Allview Soul X6 Mini', 'manufacturer': 'Allview', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy Note10 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie); One UI'}
{'device_name': 'Inoi 6i', 'manufacturer': 'Inoi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'OnePlus 7 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Oneplus', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (F1.6) + 16MP (F2.2) + 8 MP (F2.4)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP with Aperture F2.0, Face unlock, Sony IMX471 Exmor RS, Mechanical Pop-up Front Camera, Pixel size - 1.0 Î¼m, Digital image stabilization'}, 'operating_system': 'Oxygen 9.0 (Android 9.0 Pie)'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Mate 20 X 5G', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '39.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '23.79 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE Z557', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Alcatel Avalon V', 'manufacturer': 'Alcatel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Sony Xperia Ace', 'manufacturer': 'Sony', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.19 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Irbis SP541', 'manufacturer': 'Irbis', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Nokia 2.2', 'manufacturer': 'Nokia', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Honor 20i', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '24.84 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '31.96 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Wiko View 3 Lite', 'manufacturer': 'Wiko', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Doogee X100', 'manufacturer': 'Doogee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'itel A46', 'manufacturer': 'itel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Asus ZenFone Live (L2) SD430', 'manufacturer': 'ASUS', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy Xcover 4s', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie)'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo K3', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'ColorOS 6 (Android 9.0 Pie)'}
{'device_name': 'Wiko Y80', 'manufacturer': 'Wiko', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Maxvi MS502 Orion', 'manufacturer': 'Maze', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'HiSense F27', 'manufacturer': 'Hisense', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Vodafone Smart N10', 'manufacturer': 'Voyo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo Y12', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Funtouch OS (Android 9.0 Pie)'}
{'device_name': 'Asus ZenFone Live (L2) SD425', 'manufacturer': 'ASUS', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Maxvi MS531 Vega', 'manufacturer': 'Maze', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Inoi 7i', 'manufacturer': 'Inoi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Wiko Y60', 'manufacturer': 'Wiko', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'HiSense Rock V', 'manufacturer': 'Hisense', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Vodafone Smart V10', 'manufacturer': 'Voyo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Runbo E81', 'manufacturer': 'Razer', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Maxvi MS401 Sunrise', 'manufacturer': 'Maze', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'itel A44 Air', 'manufacturer': 'itel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Sharp Aquos R3', 'manufacturer': 'Sharp', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.19 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'HiSense F25', 'manufacturer': 'Hisense', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Xgody X27', 'manufacturer': 'Xtouch', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Motorola Moto E6', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Prestigio Wize U3', 'manufacturer': 'Prestigio', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': '360 (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'BQ Mobile BQ-5528L Strike Forward', 'manufacturer': 'BQ Mobile', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Realme X Lite', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '24.84 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'ColorOS 6.0 (Android 9.0 Pie)'}
{'device_name': 'HiSense F16', 'manufacturer': 'Hisense', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Blackview A60 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Blackview', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo Z3x', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Funtouch 9.0 OS (Android 9.0 Pie)'}
{'device_name': 'Realme X', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'ColorOS 6.0 (Android 9.0 Pie)'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE Blade V10 Vita', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Ark S503 (New)', 'manufacturer': 'Tecno', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Fly Life Sky', 'manufacturer': 'FLY', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Ulefone P6000 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Ulefone', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels + 5 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixel'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo Z5x', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '24.77 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Funtouch 9.0 OS (Android 9.0 Pie)'}
{'device_name': 'Sugar S30', 'manufacturer': 'Sugar', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Cubot X20', 'manufacturer': 'Cubot', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48MP+12MP+5MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels with Face Unlock'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE Axon 10 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '19.66 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Infinix Hot 7 Pro X625B', 'manufacturer': 'Infinix', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'X OS 5.0 (Android 9.0 Pie)'}
{'device_name': 'Haier Alpha A1', 'manufacturer': 'Haier', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Symphony Z15', 'manufacturer': 'Symphony', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo A1k', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Color OS 5.2.1 OS (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Sugar F20', 'manufacturer': 'Sugar', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.19 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'BLU G9', 'manufacturer': 'BLU', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Symphony i72', 'manufacturer': 'Symphony', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo Reno Z Helio P90', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48MP+12MP+5MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie); ColorOS 6'}
{'device_name': 'Sugar C13', 'manufacturer': 'Sugar', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.19 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'OnePlus 7 Pro 5G', 'manufacturer': 'Oneplus', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (F1.6) + 16MP (F2.2) + 8 MP (F2.4)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP with Aperture F2.0, Face unlock, Sony IMX471 Exmor RS, Mechanical Pop-up Front Camera, Pixel size - 1.0 Î¼m, Digital image stabilization'}, 'operating_system': 'Oxygen 9.0 (Android 9.0 Pie)'}
{'device_name': 'Symphony R40', 'manufacturer': 'Symphony', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Redmi K20 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP, f/1.8, 26mm (wide), 1/2, 0.8Âµm, PDAF, Laser AF + 8 MP, f/2.4, 53mm (telephoto), 1/4, 1.12Âµm, PDAF, Laser AF, 2x optical zoom + 13 MP, f/2.4, 12mm (ultrawide), 1/3, 1.12Âµm'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'Motorized pop-up 20 MP, f/2.2, 0.8Âµm'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie); MIUI 10'}
{'device_name': 'Walton Primo NF4', 'manufacturer': 'Walton', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'nubia mini 5G', 'manufacturer': 'Nubia', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Realme X Master Edition', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'ColorOS 6.0 (Android 9.0 Pie)'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Nova 5', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP, PDAF'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '25 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie)'}
{'device_name': 'Elephone A7', 'manufacturer': 'Elephone', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 Megapixels + 13 Megapixels + 8 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels with Face Recognition'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Honor 20 Lite', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '23.79 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '31.96 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Wiko View 3 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Wiko', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.19 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei P20 Lite 2019', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '23.79 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '19.96 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Blackview BV5500 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Blackview', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'nubia Red Magic 3', 'manufacturer': 'Nubia', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'BLU C5L', 'manufacturer': 'BLU', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'CUBOT R19', 'manufacturer': 'Cubot', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels + 2 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with Face Unlock'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei nova 5i', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '24 MP, PDAF'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie)'}
{'device_name': 'Lenovo Z6 Youth Edition', 'manufacturer': 'Lenovo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Redmi K20', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '20 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'MIUI 10 (Android 9.0 Pie)'}
{'device_name': 'Lenovo Z6 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Lenovo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '31.96 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE Blade L8', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Noa Hummer 2019', 'manufacturer': 'Noa', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE Blade A7 Helio P60', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Doogee X90', 'manufacturer': 'Doogee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'TECNO Spark 3 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Tecno', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP + 2 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie) + HIOS 5.0'}
{'device_name': 'Oukitel Y4800', 'manufacturer': 'Oukitel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.1 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Coolpad Legacy', 'manufacturer': 'Coolpad', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Redmi Note 7S', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 Megapixels f/1.8 + 5 Megapixels f/2.2 Dual Back camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels with f/2.0 Aperture, Face Recognition'}, 'operating_system': 'MIUI V10 (Android 9.0 Pie)'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE Blade A3 2019', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Tecno Spark 3', 'manufacturer': 'Tecno', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy S10 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP, f/1.5-2.4, 26mm (wide), 1/2.55, 1.4Âµm, Dual Pixel PDAF, OIS'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '10 MP, f/1.9, 26mm (wide), 1.22Âµm, Dual Pixel PDAF'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie); One UI'}
{'device_name': 'LG Solo LTE', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'iLA 8X', 'manufacturer': 'iLA', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Freeme OS 8.1 (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Xolo ZX', 'manufacturer': 'Xtouch', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Star OS (Android 9.0 Pie)'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE Blade A7', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Tecno Spark 3 1GB', 'manufacturer': 'Tecno', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Redmi 7A', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'MIUI (Android 9.0 Pie)'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy M40', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'Unknown cameras'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'Unknown camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'LG K8S', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Ðreo'}
{'device_name': 'VKworld SD200', 'manufacturer': 'VKworld', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'ColorOS 6.0 (Android 9.0 Pie)'}
{'device_name': 'LG X4 (2019)', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei P Smart Z', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Realme 3 MT6771', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'ColorOS 6.0 (Android 9.0 Pie)'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo Y15', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Funtouch OS (Android 9.0 Pie)'}
{'device_name': 'Koobee X6', 'manufacturer': 'Koobee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels + 5 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8MP with Face Recognition, F2.0 Aperture'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'DEXP B260', 'manufacturer': 'DEXP', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Meizu 16Xs', 'manufacturer': 'Meizu', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'FlyMe (Android 9.0 Pie)'}
{'device_name': 'Motorola Moto Z4 Force', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '24.77 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Wiko View 3', 'manufacturer': 'Wiko', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP, 27mm (wide), 1/2.9, 1.25Âµm, PDAF'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, PDAF'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie)'}
{'device_name': 'DEXP GS155', 'manufacturer': 'DEXP', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'VKworld SD100', 'manufacturer': 'VKworld', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'ColorOS 6.0 (Android 9.0 Pie)'}
{'device_name': 'UMIDIGI A5 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'UMiDigi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP primary camera, Sony IMX398/Samsung S5K2P7, F/1.8, 6P lens + 8 MP ultra-wide angle camera, 120Â° wide-angle + 5 MP depth camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP + 5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'ASUS Zenfone 6', 'manufacturer': 'ASUS', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 Megapixels + 13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'Motorized flip Primary camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie OS with ZENUI 6.0'}
{'device_name': 'Oukitel K13', 'manufacturer': 'Oukitel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels + 2 Megapixels (Dual Camera)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with Face Unlock, 0.18 inch Sensor Size, GalaxyCore GC8034 CMOS BSI Sensor, Pixel Size - 1.124 um'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy A40s', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Meizu 17 5G', 'manufacturer': 'Meizu', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 Megapixels + 12 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 Megapixels with CMOS Sensor, f2.0 Aperture, 1080p Video, Face Unlock'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Elephone A7H', 'manufacturer': 'Elephone', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels + 2 Megapixels + 0.3 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with Face Recognition'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo A9', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'ColorOS 6 (Android 9.0 Pie)'}
{'device_name': 'Asus Zenfone 6 ZS630KL', 'manufacturer': 'ASUS', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP, f/1.8, 26mm (wide), 1/2, 0.8Âµm, Laser/PDAF'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/2.4, 11mm (ultrawide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie), ZenUI 6'}
{'device_name': 'Symphony i65', 'manufacturer': 'Symphony', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Realme 3 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '24.84 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'ColorOS 6.0 (Android 9.0 Pie)'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE Blade A5', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Coolpad Legacy Go', 'manufacturer': 'Coolpad', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo Y93 Lite', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Funtouch 4.5 OS (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo Reno 5G', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'ColorOS 6 (Android 9.0 Pie)'}
{'device_name': 'Motorola Moto Z4', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '24.77 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Elephone U3H', 'manufacturer': 'Elephone', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 Megapixels + 5 Megapixels + 2 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16MP with Face Recognition, F2.0 Aperture'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Inoi kPhone 4G', 'manufacturer': 'Inoi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo A9x', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'ColorOS 6 (Android 9.0 Pie)'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE Blade L130', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.31 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Y5 2019', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixel with F2.0 Aperture, Face recognition, CMOS BSI'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie with EMUI 9.0'}
{'device_name': 'Google Pixel 3a XL', 'manufacturer': 'Google', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.19 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Y9 Prime 2019', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Inoi kPhone', 'manufacturer': 'Inoi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Realme C2', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'ColorOS 6.0 (Android 9.0 Pie)'}
{'device_name': 'itel A52 Lite', 'manufacturer': 'itel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Micromax iOne', 'manufacturer': 'Micromax', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Ulefone Note 7', 'manufacturer': 'Ulefone', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12MP+5MP+5MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with Face Recognition'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Allview Soul X6 Xtreme', 'manufacturer': 'Allview', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Infinix Hot 7 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Infinix', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'X OS 5.0 (Android 9.0 Pie)'}
{'device_name': 'Xgody P20 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Xtouch', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Elephone U3', 'manufacturer': 'Elephone', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 Megapixels + 5 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16MP with Face Recognition, F2.0 Aperture'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo Reno Z', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48MP+12MP+5MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 (Oreo); ColorOS 5.2'}
{'device_name': 'Oukitel K12', 'manufacturer': 'Oukitel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Allview P10 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Allview', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 OreÐ¾ Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Archos Core 62S', 'manufacturer': 'Archos', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Mate 20 Lite', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '20 MP (F1.8) + 2 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '24 MP + 2 MP with F2.0 Aperture, CMOS BSI Sensor'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo Y17', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Funtouch OS (Android 9.0 Pie)'}
{'device_name': 'Cubot J7', 'manufacturer': 'Cubot', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels + 2 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with Interpolated Resolution 8MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo Y3', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Funtouch OS 4.0 (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Honor 20', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48MP +20MP + 8MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 Megapixels with F2.0 Aperture, CMOS BSI Sensor'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Redmi Y3', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.19 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '31.96 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'MIUI V10 (Android 9.0 Pie)'}
{'device_name': 'BQ Mobile BQ-6040L Magic', 'manufacturer': 'BQ Mobile', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Honor 20 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48MP +20MP + 8MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 Megapixels with F2.0 Aperture, CMOS BSI Sensor'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Ulefone Armor 6E', 'manufacturer': 'Ulefone', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Tecno Camon 11S', 'manufacturer': 'Tecno', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'HiOS 4.6 (Android 9.0 Pie)'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo Y5', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Infinix Smart 3 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Infinix', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Honor 8S', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Prestigio Muze K3 LTE', 'manufacturer': 'Prestigio', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': '360 (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Prestigio Wize V3', 'manufacturer': 'Prestigio', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': '360 (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'E&L S618', 'manufacturer': 'EL', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Infinix Hot S4', 'manufacturer': 'Infinix', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, PDAF + 8 MP + 2 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie)'}
{'device_name': 'E&L S55', 'manufacturer': 'EL', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy A90 (RUMORED)', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP + 8 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '24 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Motorola One Vision', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '12.19 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy A80', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP, f/1.8, 1/2, 0.8Âµm, PDAF'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'Flipping main camera module'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Fly Power Plus 5000', 'manufacturer': 'FLY', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo Reno 10x zoom', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + Periscope 13 MP (telephoto), 5x optical zoom + 8 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'Motorized pop-up 16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie) + ColorOS 6'}
{'device_name': 'Zen Admire Shine', 'manufacturer': 'Zoji', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Cubot Max 2', 'manufacturer': 'Cubot', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.19 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'UMIDIGI F1 Play', 'manufacturer': 'UMiDigi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16.37 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16.37 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Allview P10 Max', 'manufacturer': 'Allview', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 OreÐ¾ Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Leagoo Z10', 'manufacturer': 'Leagoo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '0.31 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Lava Z40', 'manufacturer': 'Lava', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Cubot R15', 'manufacturer': 'Cubot', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Lenovo K9 Note', 'manufacturer': 'Lenovo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Allview P10 Mini', 'manufacturer': 'Allview', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 OreÐ¾ Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Irbis SP493', 'manufacturer': 'Irbis', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Lenovo K6 Enjoy', 'manufacturer': 'Lenovo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.19 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Enjoy 9e', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Jinga Hit 4G', 'manufacturer': 'Jinga', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'HomTom HT16S', 'manufacturer': 'Homtom', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': '360 (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Geecoo G1 3G', 'manufacturer': 'Geecoo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '0.31 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Nokia 9 PureView', 'manufacturer': 'Nokia', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 Megapixels X 5 + TOF (Five Rear Camera)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '20 MP with 1.0Âµm'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie Android One'}
{'device_name': 'DOOGEE N10', 'manufacturer': 'Doogee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels + 2 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Nobby S300', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'TP-LINK Neffos C7 Lite', 'manufacturer': 'TP-LINK', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Redmi 7', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.19 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'MIUI (Android 9.0 Pie)'}
{'device_name': 'BQ Mobile BQ-5004G Fox', 'manufacturer': 'BQ Mobile', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Nokia 5', 'manufacturer': 'Nokia', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with F2.0 aperture,1.12Âµm sensor,84 degree wide angle lens'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie Android One'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo S1', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.19 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '23.79 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Funtouch OS (Android 9.0 Pie)'}
{'device_name': 'Leagoo M13', 'manufacturer': 'Leagoo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Blackview A60', 'manufacturer': 'Blackview', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Elephone A6 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Elephone', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 Megapixels + 8 Megapixels + 5 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '20 Megapixels with Face Recognition'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy A2 Core', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei nova 4e', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '21.27 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32.33 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Nobby A200', 'manufacturer': 'Nomu', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '0.31 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Meizu Note 9', 'manufacturer': 'Meizu', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'FlyMe (Android 9.0 Pie)'}
{'device_name': 'Nomu M8', 'manufacturer': 'Nomu', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '21.46 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '21.46 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'HomTom S77', 'manufacturer': 'Homtom', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels + 2 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo F11', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'ColorOS 6.0 (Android 9.0 Pie)'}
{'device_name': 'Nobby S500', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo X27 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Funtouch OS (Android 9.0 Pie)'}
{'device_name': 'Walton Primo G8i', 'manufacturer': 'Walton', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Texet TM-5083 Pay 5', 'manufacturer': 'Texet', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'LG K12+', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'RugGear RG725', 'manufacturer': 'Razer', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Honor 8A Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Casper VIA A2', 'manufacturer': 'Cenava', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '19.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.2 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Oukitel C14 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Oukitel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels + 0.3 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Walton Primo EM2', 'manufacturer': 'Walton', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Panasonic Eluga Ray 800', 'manufacturer': 'Panasonic', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Panasonic P110', 'manufacturer': 'Panasonic', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Mi 9X', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP, f/1.8, 27mm (wide), 1/2, 0.8Âµm, PDAF'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP, f/2.0'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie); MIUI 10'}
{'device_name': 'DEXP B340', 'manufacturer': 'DEXP', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Walton Primo E9 Exclusive', 'manufacturer': 'Walton', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'RugGear RG650', 'manufacturer': 'Razer', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Y7 2019', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'itel A16 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'itel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '0.31 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Sony Xperia 10', 'manufacturer': 'Sony', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/2.0, 27mm (wide), 1/3, 1.12Âµm, PDAF'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, f/2.0, 24mm (wide), 1/4, 1.12Âµm'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Walton Primo H8', 'manufacturer': 'Walton', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Casper VIA G3', 'manufacturer': 'Cenava', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.19 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Walton Primo E9', 'manufacturer': 'Walton', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Tecno Camon i 4 2GB', 'manufacturer': 'Tecno', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'HiOS 4.1 (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Sony Xperia 1', 'manufacturer': 'Sony', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP, f/1.6, 26mm (wide), 1/2.6, 1.4Âµm, predictive Dual Pixel PDAF, 5-axis OIS'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, f/2.0, 24mm (wide), 1/4, 1.0Âµm'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie)'}
{'device_name': 'Cyrus CS45', 'manufacturer': 'Celkon', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Casper VIA A3', 'manufacturer': 'Cenava', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.19 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Casper VIA A3 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Cenava', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'HomTom H5', 'manufacturer': 'Homtom', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': '360 (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo X27', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Funtouch OS (Android 9.0 Pie)'}
{'device_name': 'Doogee X90L', 'manufacturer': 'Doogee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels + 2 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with Face Unlock'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Tecno Camon i 4', 'manufacturer': 'Tecno', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'HiOS 4.1 (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Meizu Note 9 Lite', 'manufacturer': 'Meizu', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 Megapixels + 5 Megapixels Dual Back camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with F2.0 Aperture, Face Recognition'}, 'operating_system': 'Flyme OS (Android 9.0 Pie)'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy A40', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '24.77 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Asus ZenFone Max Shot', 'manufacturer': 'ASUS', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Xgody X25', 'manufacturer': 'Xtouch', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Sharp Aquos Keitai 3', 'manufacturer': 'Sharp', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'NA'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 5.1.1 Lollipop'}
{'device_name': 'Doogee S40', 'manufacturer': 'Doogee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy A20e', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo X27 128GB', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Funtouch OS (Android 9.0 Pie)'}
{'device_name': 'Vestel Venus E4', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Asus ZenFone Max Plus (M2)', 'manufacturer': 'ASUS', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Oukitel C13 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Oukitel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels + 0.3 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Enjoy 9s', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '24 MP (F2.2) + 16 MP (ultra-wide angle) + 2 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixel with F2.0 Aperture, CMOS BSI Sensor'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Sigma Mobile X-treme PQ29', 'manufacturer': 'Sigma', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Realme 3', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'ColorOS 6.0 (Android 9.0 Pie)'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Honor 10i', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '23.79 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '31.96 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Prestigio S Max', 'manufacturer': 'Prestigio', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': '360 (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Xgody S10', 'manufacturer': 'Xtouch', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Conquest S9 MT6757', 'manufacturer': 'Celkon', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.1 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Mi 9 Lite', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP + 8 MP + 2 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP, f/2.0, 0.8Âµm'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie) + MIUI 10'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo iQOO', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.19 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '12.19 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Funtouch 9.0 OS (Android 9.0 Pie)'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy A20', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide) AF + 5 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie) + One UI'}
{'device_name': 'RugGear RG655', 'manufacturer': 'Razer', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'UMiDIGI Power', 'manufacturer': 'UMiDigi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels + 8 Megapixels Dual Back camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP with Face unlock'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei P30 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '40 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '20 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo AX5s', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'ColorOS 5.1 (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Xgody XR', 'manufacturer': 'Xtouch', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Infinix Zero 6 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Infinix', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.19 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '19.66 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Xgody P20', 'manufacturer': 'Xtouch', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Nokia 8.1 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Nokia', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP + 8 MP (ultra-wide angle) + 5 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels with F2.0 Aperture, Carl Zeiss Lens'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Tecno Camon i Sky 3', 'manufacturer': 'Tecno', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'HiOS 4.1 (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo V15', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.19 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32.33 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Funtouch 9.0 OS (Android 9.0 Pie)'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei P30', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '40 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy A70', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 5 MP depth'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie) + One UI'}
{'device_name': 'Infinix Zero 6', 'manufacturer': 'Infinix', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.19 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '19.66 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Black Shark 2', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '20.11 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo Reno Lite', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16MP+2MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels with Face Unlock, F2.0 Aperture'}, 'operating_system': 'ColorOS 6 (Android 9.0 Pie)'}
{'device_name': 'Ulefone S11', 'manufacturer': 'Ulefone', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12MP+5MP+5MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with Face Recognition'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei P30 Lite', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP depth sensor or 24 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP depth sensor'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '24 MP or 32 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie) + EMUI 9.1'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Mi A3 Lite (RUMORED)', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP + 5 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 GB'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'HiSense U30', 'manufacturer': 'Hisense', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '21.27 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'PROTRULY Darling V10S', 'manufacturer': 'Plum', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 Oreo Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Meizu 16S', 'manufacturer': 'Meizu', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 Megapixels f/1.8, 1.55 Âµm + 20 Megapixels 1.0 Âµm'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '20 Megapixels f/2.0, 1080P with Face Unlock Feature, AI Powered'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Vestel Venus Z30', 'manufacturer': 'Vernee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Kenxinda S60X', 'manufacturer': 'Kult', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels + 0.3 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with Aperture F2.0, Face Unlock, 4P Lens'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Asus ZenFone Max Pro (M1)', 'manufacturer': 'ASUS', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels + 5 Megapixels (16MP + 5MP For 6GB Version)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixel (16MP 6GB Version) with Face Recognition, 1.0 um Pixel Size, LED Flashlight,'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Pocophone F1 Lite', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 Megapixels + 5 Megapixels Dual Back camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with Face Recognition'}, 'operating_system': 'MIUI V10 (Android 9.0 Pie)'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo A5s (AX5s)', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/2.2, AF + 2 MP, f/2.4, depth sensor'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, f/2.0'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 (Oreo); ColorOS 5.2'}
{'device_name': 'Cubot Quest Lite', 'manufacturer': 'Cubot', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Asus Zenfone 6Z', 'manufacturer': 'ASUS', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 Megapixels + 16 Megapixels + 8 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '20 Megapixel with Face Recognition'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Hisense King Kong 5 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Hisense', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels + 2 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Vestel Venus V7', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Kenxinda W51', 'manufacturer': 'Kult', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '0.31 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Cubot J5', 'manufacturer': 'Cubot', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Pocophone F2 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64MP main, 8MP ultra-wide and 16MP telephoto cameras'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '20 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'MIUI 10 (Android 10)'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo A7n', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '24.84 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Color OS 5.2.1 OS (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo Y91i India', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels f/2.2'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with f/1.8 Aperture, Face Recognition'}, 'operating_system': 'Funtouch 4.5 OS (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Ulefone Power 3L', 'manufacturer': 'Ulefone', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Kenxinda W41', 'manufacturer': 'Kult', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '0.31 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '0.31 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'General Mobile GM 9 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'General Mobile', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.19 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Nokia X71', 'manufacturer': 'Nokia', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP + 8 MP (ultra-wide angle) + 5 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels with F2.0 Aperture, Carl Zeiss Lens'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Doogee Y8C', 'manufacturer': 'Doogee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Hisense King Kong 5', 'manufacturer': 'Hisense', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels + 2 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'General Mobile GM 9 Go', 'manufacturer': 'General Mobile', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Doogee Y8 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Doogee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo OS'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo Reno', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48MP+12MP+5MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels with Face Unlock'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 (Oreo); ColorOS 5.2'}
{'device_name': 'Kenxinda 6A', 'manufacturer': 'Kult', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '0.31 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'itel A16', 'manufacturer': 'itel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '0.31 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'General Mobile GM 8 Go', 'manufacturer': 'General Mobile', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'HomTom C13', 'manufacturer': 'Homtom', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels + 2 Megapixels Samsung'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with Face Unlock, Interpolated resolution 8 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go edition'}
{'device_name': 'OnePlus 7', 'manufacturer': 'Oneplus', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 5MP depth sensor'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie) + OxygenOS 9.5.8'}
{'device_name': 'Prestigio Grace V7 LTE', 'manufacturer': 'Prestigio', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': '360 (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei P smart+ 2019', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '23.79 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Redmi Pro 2', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP + 16 MP + 8 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '20 Megapixels with F2.2 Aperture, Face Recognition'}, 'operating_system': 'MIUI V10 (Android 9.0 Pie)'}
{'device_name': 'NUU Mobile A5L Plus', 'manufacturer': 'DEXP', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Energizer Power Max P551S', 'manufacturer': 'Energizer', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'AGM X3 Turbo', 'manufacturer': 'AGM', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.19 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '19.66 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'X OS 3.0 (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Infinix Hot 7', 'manufacturer': 'Infinix', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, AF + QVGA, depth sensor'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo + Go edition'}
{'device_name': 'Centric S1', 'manufacturer': 'Comio', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Prestigio X Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Prestigio', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Oukitel K9', 'manufacturer': 'Oukitel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Honor Magic 2 3D', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Centric G3', 'manufacturer': 'Comio', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.19 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo Y91i MT6762', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Funtouch 4.5 OS (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Centric G5', 'manufacturer': 'Comio', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy A60', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Centric A2', 'manufacturer': 'Comio', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Inoi 5i Lite', 'manufacturer': 'Inoi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Centric L4', 'manufacturer': 'Comio', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE Blade V10', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32.33 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Tecno Camon i Ace2x', 'manufacturer': 'Tecno', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'HiOS 4.1 (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Energizer Ultimate U630S Pop', 'manufacturer': 'Energizer', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Blackview Max 1', 'manufacturer': 'Blackview', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Tecno Camon i Ace2', 'manufacturer': 'Tecno', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'HiOS 4.1 (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Alcatel 1V', 'manufacturer': 'Alcatel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE Axon 10 Pro 5G', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP f/1.7 (primary) + 8MP f/2.4 (telephoto) + 20MP f/2.2 (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '20MP MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'LG G8 ThinQ', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Ðreo'}
{'device_name': 'DEXP G253', 'manufacturer': 'DEXP', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Archos Oxygen 68 XL', 'manufacturer': 'Archos', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'BLU Studio X8 HD 2019', 'manufacturer': 'BLU', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Walton Primo R5 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Walton', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Alcatel 1S', 'manufacturer': 'Alcatel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Elephone A6 Mini', 'manufacturer': 'Elephone', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Energizer Ultimate U620S Pop', 'manufacturer': 'Energizer', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'DEXP B355', 'manufacturer': 'DEXP', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Motorola Moto Z4 Play', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Jinga Win Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Jinga', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Sony Xperia L3', 'manufacturer': 'Sony', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Y6 Pro 2019', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie) + EMUI 9'}
{'device_name': 'Archos Oxygen 63', 'manufacturer': 'Archos', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Land Rover X', 'manufacturer': 'Lanix', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Y6 2019', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'DEXP BS155', 'manufacturer': 'DEXP', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Redmi Go', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Energizer Ultimate U620S', 'manufacturer': 'Energizer', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Sony Xperia 10 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Sony', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.19 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Highscreen Wallet', 'manufacturer': 'Haier', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy Fold', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.19 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '10.51 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'General Mobile GM 9 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'General Mobile', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.2 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Jinga Start LTE', 'manufacturer': 'Jinga', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Energizer Hardcase H501S', 'manufacturer': 'Energizer', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Realme C1 (2019)', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'ColorOS 5.1 (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'DEXP GS150', 'manufacturer': 'DEXP', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Jinga Pass 3G', 'manufacturer': 'Jinga', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Energizer Ultimate U570S', 'manufacturer': 'Sugar', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Archos Oxygen 57', 'manufacturer': 'Archos', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Energizer Hardcase H570S', 'manufacturer': 'Energizer', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'BQ Mobile BQ-4001G Cool', 'manufacturer': 'BQ Mobile', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '0.31 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Energizer Hardcase H591S', 'manufacturer': 'Energizer', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Meizu Zero', 'manufacturer': 'Meizu', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 Megapixels + 20 Megapixels (Telephoto)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '20 MP with Aperture F2.0, Face Unlock'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Noa N20', 'manufacturer': 'Noa', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'China Mobile A3S', 'manufacturer': 'Sugar', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with F2.0 Aperture, OmniVision OV5670 PureCel Sensor, F2.4 Aperture, 5P Lens'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'DEXP AS260', 'manufacturer': 'DEXP', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'LG V50 ThinQ 5G', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.19 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Noa F20 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Noa', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'LG Q9 One', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16.26 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Coolpad Cool 3', 'manufacturer': 'Coolpad', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Sony Xperia XZ4', 'manufacturer': 'Sony', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '19.2 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Noa F10 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Noa', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '21.27 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '24.77 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Energizer Energy E401', 'manufacturer': 'Energizer', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Motorola Moto G7 Power', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.58 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Inoi 5i Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Inoi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Xgody Mate RS', 'manufacturer': 'Xtouch', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Alcatel 1 (2019)', 'manufacturer': 'Alcatel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo Y91C (RUMORED)', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Funtouch 4.5 OS (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Karbonn Vue 1', 'manufacturer': 'Karbonn', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Motorola Moto G7 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.58 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Mi 9 Explorer Edition', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '19.66 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'MIUI (Android 9.0 Pie)'}
{'device_name': 'Nokia 1 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Nokia', 'rear_camera': {}, 'front_camera': {}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'BQ Mobile BQ-5011G Fox View', 'manufacturer': 'BQ Mobile', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy S10e Exynos', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.19 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'HomTom S99i', 'manufacturer': 'Homtom', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels + 2 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with Face Unlock'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Energizer Energy E551S', 'manufacturer': 'Energizer', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Motorola Moto G7 Play', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Nokia 2 V', 'manufacturer': 'Nokia', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy S10 5G Exynos', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.19 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '10.51 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Motorola Moto G7', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.58 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy S10e SD855', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.19 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Nokia 4.2', 'manufacturer': 'Nokia', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy J2 Pure', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'BQ Mobile BQ-5514G Strike Power', 'manufacturer': 'BQ Mobile', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Cubot Max 2', 'manufacturer': 'Cubot', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels + 16 Megapixels (Dual Camera)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Symphony i95', 'manufacturer': 'Symphony', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': '360 3.0 (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Assistant AS-601L Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Assistant', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Nokia 3.2', 'manufacturer': 'Nokia', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Symphony V48', 'manufacturer': 'Symphony', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Blackview BV9700 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Blackview', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels + 8 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8MP with Face Recognition'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Assistant AS-401L Asper', 'manufacturer': 'Assistant', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Mate X', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '9.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '24.79 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie); EMUI 9.1'}
{'device_name': 'Sigma Mobile X-style S5501', 'manufacturer': 'Sigma', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Oukitel C15 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Oukitel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy S10 5G SD855', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.19 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '10.51 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Oukitel C10 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Oukitel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Black Fox B7Fox Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Bravis', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Symphony V97', 'manufacturer': 'Symphony', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Symphony V142', 'manufacturer': 'Symphony', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Black Fox B7', 'manufacturer': 'Bravis', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'ioutdoor Polar3', 'manufacturer': 'ioutdoor', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels + 2 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with Face Unlock'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Micromax Canvas Curve Q454', 'manufacturer': 'Micromax', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Mi Mix 3 5G', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.19 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '24.84 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'MIUI V10 (Android 9.0 Pie)'}
{'device_name': 'Inoi 6i Lite', 'manufacturer': 'Inoi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Infinix Smart 2 Go Edition', 'manufacturer': 'Infinix', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Black Fox B6Fox', 'manufacturer': 'Bravis', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Kyocera Otegaru 01', 'manufacturer': 'Kyocera', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Walton Primo D9', 'manufacturer': 'Walton', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '0.31 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Digma Linx Argo 3G', 'manufacturer': 'Digma', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '0.31 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Archos Diamond', 'manufacturer': 'Archos', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Sharp Aquos SH-02L', 'manufacturer': 'Sharp', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'NA'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 5.1.1 Lollipop'}
{'device_name': 'Walton Primo GM3+ (3GB)', 'manufacturer': 'Walton', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE Blade A606', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'LG K40', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Ðreo'}
{'device_name': 'Kogan Agora XS', 'manufacturer': 'Konka', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.19 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Jinga Neon', 'manufacturer': 'Jinga', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'NA'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Black Fox B6', 'manufacturer': 'Bravis', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo F11 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'ColorOS 6.0 (Android 9.0 Pie)'}
{'device_name': 'Leagoo XRover C', 'manufacturer': 'Leagoo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Leagoo OS 3.0 (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Symphony V128', 'manufacturer': 'Symphony', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Black Fox B4 mini NFC', 'manufacturer': 'Blackview', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Gigaset GS280', 'manufacturer': 'Gigaset', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'LG K50', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Ðreo'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo Y89', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels + 2 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels with F2.0 Aperture, Face Recognition'}, 'operating_system': 'Funtouch OS 4.0 (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Kogan Agora 8', 'manufacturer': 'Konka', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo V15 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 5 MP depth sensor'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'Motorized pop-up 32 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie) + Funtouch 9'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei nova Lite 3', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Black Fox B4 mini', 'manufacturer': 'Blackview', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Alcatel 3V', 'manufacturer': 'Alcatel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0'}
{'device_name': 'Coolpad Cool Play 8 Lite', 'manufacturer': 'Coolpad', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'BLU C6L', 'manufacturer': 'BLU', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'LG Q60', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Ðreo'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Mi 9 SE', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '19.66 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'MIUI V10 (Android 9.0 Pie)'}
{'device_name': 'Kogan Agora 9', 'manufacturer': 'Konka', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Alcatel 3L', 'manufacturer': 'Alcatel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie and Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy S10 Plus Exynos', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.19 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Mi 9 Transparent Edition', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '20.11 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'MIUI V10 (Android 9.0 Pie)'}
{'device_name': 'Philips S562Z', 'manufacturer': 'Phillips', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'LG Tribute Empire', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy S10 Plus SD855', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.19 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Energizer Power Max P18K Pop', 'manufacturer': 'Energizer', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Gionee F205 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Gionee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy S10 Exynos', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.19 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Alcatel 3C', 'manufacturer': 'Alcatel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Oukitel C12', 'manufacturer': 'Oukitel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'LG Aristo 3', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Alcatel 3 (2019)', 'manufacturer': 'Alcatel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy J7 TopA10', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy S10 SD855', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.19 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo U1', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Funtouch 4.5 OS (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Lenovo A5s', 'manufacturer': 'Lenovo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Lava Z92', 'manufacturer': 'Lava', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Vsmart Active 1 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Vernee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '23.79 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '19.96 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'VOS (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy A30', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy A50', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '24.24 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '24.24 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo Y85 MT6762', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Funtouch 4.0 OS (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Vsmart Active 1', 'manufacturer': 'Vernee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.19 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'VOS (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE Vision R2', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Vsmart Joy 1 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'VKworld', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'BQ Mobile BQ-5010G Spot', 'manufacturer': 'BQ Mobile', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Vsmart Joy 1', 'manufacturer': 'Alcatel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'BQ Mobile BQ-5521L Rich Max', 'manufacturer': 'BQ Mobile', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'BQ Mobile BQ-6010G Practic', 'manufacturer': 'BQ Mobile', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'BQ Mobile BQ-5519L Fast Plus', 'manufacturer': 'BQ Mobile', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE Blade A622', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'AllCall S5500', 'manufacturer': 'AllCall', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Vertex Impress Stone', 'manufacturer': 'Vertex', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Alcatel Onyx', 'manufacturer': 'Alcatel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy A9 Pro (2018)', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '24 MP (wide) + 10 MP (telephoto) 2x optical zoom + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 5 MP (wide) depth sensor'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '24 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 (Oreo), upgradable to Android 9.0 (Pie)'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Y7 Prime 2019', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'BQ Mobile BQ-5514L Strike Power 4G', 'manufacturer': 'BQ Mobile', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Jinga Picasso Note', 'manufacturer': 'Jinga', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Redmi Note 7 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 5 MP depth sensor'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie) + MIUI 10'}
{'device_name': 'Sugar C21', 'manufacturer': 'Sugar', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.19 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Haier Elegance E9', 'manufacturer': 'Haier', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Sugar Y16', 'manufacturer': 'Sugar', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'itel A44 Power', 'manufacturer': 'itel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'iLA 7R', 'manufacturer': 'iLA', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.1 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Meizu Note 9', 'manufacturer': 'Meizu', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'FlyMe (Android 9.0 Pie)'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Redmi Note 7', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 5 MP depth sensor or 12 MP (wide) + 2 MP depth sensor'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie) + MIUI 10'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo Y91 (Mediatek)', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP + 2 MP depth sensor'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 (Oreo) + Funtouch 4.5'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaolajiao 7R', 'manufacturer': 'Ticwatch', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.1 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Xolo Era 5X', 'manufacturer': 'Xtouch', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Leagoo S11', 'manufacturer': 'Leagoo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Leagoo OS (Android 9.0 Pie)'}
{'device_name': 'Fly View', 'manufacturer': 'FLY', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Infinix Smart 2 HD', 'manufacturer': 'Infinix', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'BLU Vivo One Plus 2019', 'manufacturer': 'BLU', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Archos Access 50 S', 'manufacturer': 'Archos', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Doogee S90', 'manufacturer': 'Doogee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Alcatel 1X (2019)', 'manufacturer': 'Alcatel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Cubot X19', 'manufacturer': 'Cubot', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Alcatel 1C (2019)', 'manufacturer': 'Alcatel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Micromax Bolt Prime Q306', 'manufacturer': 'Micromax', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '0.31 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Irbis SP554', 'manufacturer': 'Irbis', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Sharp Android One S5', 'manufacturer': 'Sharp', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.19 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Micromax Q4151', 'manufacturer': 'Micromax', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'MyPhone Fun 7 LTE', 'manufacturer': 'MyPhone', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Micromax Bolt Q357', 'manufacturer': 'Micromax', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '0.31 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'MyPhone Fun 6 Lite', 'manufacturer': 'MyPhone', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '0.31 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'MyPhone Hammer Active 2 LTE', 'manufacturer': 'MyPhone', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Noa N10', 'manufacturer': 'Noa', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'MyPhone Hammer Blade 2 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'MyPhone', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Noa P1', 'manufacturer': 'Noa', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'nubia X', 'manufacturer': 'Nubia', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Noa Fresh 4G', 'manufacturer': 'Noa', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Blackview BV5500', 'manufacturer': 'Blackview', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Doogee Y8', 'manufacturer': 'Doogee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo OS'}
{'device_name': 'Noa Primo 4G', 'manufacturer': 'Noa', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Noa Vivo 4G', 'manufacturer': 'Noa', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Noa N1', 'manufacturer': 'Noa', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Allview P10 Life', 'manufacturer': 'Allview', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 OreÐ¾'}
{'device_name': 'Mobiistar X1 Notch', 'manufacturer': 'Mobiistar', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
